Robert Dunham fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
Robert Dunham fonds
1963 - 1989
F-127
Q104444673
25 cm of textual records
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department Maggie Benston Student Services Building, Rm. 0400 8888 University Dr. Burnaby British Columbia Canada V5A 1S6 Telephone: 778.782.3805 Email: archives@sfu.ca http://www.sfu.ca/archives
Dunham, Robert
Robert Dunham (1939-1990) was a professor of English at Simon Fraser University. His specialty was the literature of the Romantic Period. A graduate of Stanford University, Dunham joined SFU in 1966. He was a gifted teacher who won the University's excellence in teaching award in 1986 as well as the 3M Fellowship in 1988, a national award which recognized excellence in teaching and educational leadership.
published
Full
Revised
Title of the fonds is based on its provenance.
The fonds consists of records arising from Dunham's teaching and research activities. Includes lecture and research notes, course outlines, exams and study questions, reading lists, reprints, essays and other writing by Dunham, and a few pieces of correspondence regarding Dunham's career and projects.
The materials were arranged by the Archivist.
Arts and culture
Robin Blaser donated the fonds to the SFU Archives in 1994.
All accessions have been processed as of September 2002. No further accruals are expected.
File list is available.
- Correspondence, 1967 - 1986; F-127-0-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 127-1)
  published
  Textual records
  Open
- Essays and other writing, 1963 - 1988; F-127-0-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 127-1)
- Paper The Mill on the Floss, 1967 - 1989; F-127-0-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 127-1)
- Blake, 1967 - 1989; F-127-0-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 127-1)
- Byron, 1967 - 1989; F-127-0-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 127-1)
- Coleridge, 1967 - 1989; F-127-0-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 127-1)
- English 102, 1967 - 1989; F-127-0-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 127-1)
- Exams and study questions - ENGL 101, 102, 206, 324, 326, 374, 1967 - 1989; F-127-0-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 127-1)
- Keats 1/2, 1967 - 1989; F-127-0-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 127-2)
- Keats 2/2, 1967 - 1989; F-127-0-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 127-2)
- Poetry explanations, 1967 - 1989; F-127-0-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 127-2)
- Romantic and Victorian literature - ENGL 206, 1967 - 1989; F-127-0-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 127-2)
- Romanticism - ENGL 406 and 456, 1967 - 1989; F-127-0-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 127-2)
- Seventeenth century prose and verse - ENGL 314, 1967 - 1989; F-127-0-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 127-2)
- Shakespeare, 1967 - 1989; F-127-0-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 127-2)
- Shakespeare, Coleridge and Shelley, 1967 - 1989; F-127-0-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 127-2)
- Shelley, 1967 - 1989; F-127-0-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 127-2)
- Wordsworth, 1967 - 1989; F-127-0-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 127-2)